Perfiles UP051
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Perfiles
1983 -- 1992
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
UP051
0.5 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Perfiles, a journal which, as of 1988, was published by the Tufts Collective on Latin America. An inter-disciplinary, multi-language journal that includes essays, poems, fiction, and photographs by students, faculty, and community members, with a focus on Latin America and the Caribbean. It contains annual issues from 1983 to 1992.
- Perfiles, 1983 -- 1992; UP051.001; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Perfiles, a journal which, as of 1988, was published by the Tufts Collective on Latin America. An inter-disciplinary, multi-language journal that includes essays, poems, fiction, and photographs by students, faculty, and community members, with a focus on Latin America and the Caribbean.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Perfiles, 1983; UP051.001.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 25.7 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1984; UP051.001.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 64.8 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1985; UP051.001.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 65.7 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1986; UP051.001.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 79.6 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1988; UP051.001.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 20.5 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1989; UP051.001.001.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 35.3 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1990; UP051.001.001.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 37.0 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1992; UP051.001.001.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 91.4 Megabytes (Box 1)
  - Perfiles, 1987; UP051.001.001.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 38.0 Megabytes (Box 1)